在某个时候，你和斯卡洛尼谈到了这支球队的 10 号球衣。
At some point you and Scaloni talked about the number 10 that this team has.
En algún momento vos y Scaloni hablaron de los número 10 que tiene esta selección.
你看到他们今天打得怎么样了吗？
Did you see how they played today?
¿Viste cómo jugaron hoy?
球队已经打了很长时间了。
The team has been playing for a long time.
Hace tiempo que la selección viene jugando.
这样我们就有很多人打得很好，打得舒服。
In this way we have many people who play very well, who feel comfortable playing.
De esta manera tenemos mucha gente que juega muy bien, que se siente cómodo jugando.
字里行间，这有多么困难。
between the lines with how difficult that is.
entre líneas con lo difícil que eso es.
尼科首次亮相，他也有很多品质，非常...
Nico made his debut, who also has a lot of quality, a very...
Debutó Nico, que también tiene muchísima calidad, un chico muy...
非常年轻，他完全理解比赛，他的教练是我的朋友，我了解他，他让他成长。
very young, who understands the game perfectly, who is with a coach who is a friend, I know him and he makes him grow.
muy joven, que entiende perfectamente el juego, que está con un entrenador que es amigo, lo conozco y lo hace crecer.
很多而且很好，我希望球员继续出现。
A lot and good, I hope players continue to appear.
Muchísimo y bueno, ojalá sigan apareciendo jugadores.
这种类型的，我们可以继续制作这个我们非常喜欢的游戏。
of this type and we can continue making this game that we like so much.
de este tipo y podamos seguir haciendo este juego que tanto nos gusta.
我不想让你觉得自己老了，当你在头等舱首次亮相时，尼科·帕斯还没有出生。
I don't want to make you feel old, Nico Paz wasn't born when you debuted in first class.
No te quiero hacer sentir viejo, Nico Paz no había nacido cuando debutaste en primera
是的，我知道，我知道。
Yes, I know, I know.
Sí, lo sé, lo sé.
事实是，正如我刚才所说，这太疯狂了。
The truth is, well, it's crazy, as I just said.
La verdad que, bueno, es la locura, como dije recién.
他是一位有头脑的球员...
He is a player who has a head...
Es un jugador que tiene una cabeza...
令人印象深刻，这就是为什么它是现在的样子，我希望它继续增长，我们可以做到
impressive, that's why it is where it is and I hope it continues to grow and we can do it
impresionante, por eso está donde está y ojalá siga creciendo y nosotros lo podamos
继续帮助我们球队成长，就像他今天所做的那样，当他首次亮相时，他踢了一分钟，踢球，享受比赛。
continue helping our side grow, as he did today, when he debuted, had a minute, played, enjoyed.
seguir ayudando a crecer de nuestro lado, como hizo hoy, que debutó, tuvo minuto, jugó, disfrutó.
我认为他在这支球队也会感觉很舒服，因为我们有很多球权，他是伴随着球权长大的。
And I think he will feel comfortable on this team too, because we have the ball a lot and he grew up with that.
y creo que él en este equipo se va a sentir cómodo también, pues tenemos mucho la pelota y él creció con eso.
它有很多品质。
It has a lot of quality.
tiene mucha calidad.
好吧，尼科，我想这是你永远不会忘记的一天，我们也知道你等了很长时间。
Well Nico, it's a day that I imagine you will never forget and we also know that you waited a long time.
Bueno Nico, es un día que imagino que no vas a olvidar nunca y que aparte sabemos que esperaste mucho.
不，不，是的，是的，毫无疑问，这是我一生中最美好的日子之一，事实是......
No, no, yes, yes, without a doubt, one of the most beautiful days of my life, the truth is...
No, no, sí, sí, sin duda, de los días más bonitos de mi vida, la verdad que...
这是一个梦，我简直不敢相信正在发生的事情，我很高兴。
It was a dream, I couldn't believe what was happening and I was very happy.
que ha sido un sueño, no me estaba creyendo lo que pasaba y muy feliz.
你和你的老人谈过，你的老人为国家队效力，那是世界杯，我想已经是这样了，他对你说了什么？
You talked to your old man, your old man played for the national team, it was a World Cup, I imagine that already, what did he say to you?
Hablaste con tu viejo, tu viejo jugó en la selección, fue un mundial, imagino que ya, ¿qué te dijo?
对他来说这也是一个梦想，这就是为什么我刚刚把球衣送给了他，他比我更兴奋。
For him it is also a dream and that is why I just gave him the shirt and he is more excited than me.
Para él también es un sueño y por eso nada más le di la camiseta y está más ilusionado que yo.
尼古拉斯，每次你拿球时都能感受到阿根廷球迷为你加油，这让你感到多么高兴。
Nicolás, how happy it gave you to feel the Argentine fans cheering you on every time you took the ball.
Nicolás, qué alegría te dio sentir a los hinchas argentinos alentándote cada vez que tomabas la pelota.
一种难以置信的感觉，事实是我非常高兴。
An incredible feeling and the truth is that I am very happy.
Una sensación increíble y la verdad que muy feliz.
简单介绍一下你的首次亮相吗？
A few words about your debut?
¿Unas palabras sobre tu debut?
在这个体育场里和所有人在一起我感觉很舒服。
I felt very comfortable in this stadium with all the people.
Me sentí muy cómodo en este estadio con toda la gente.
像他们一样欢呼，我内心感到很舒服，我很高兴。
cheering like they cheered and I felt very comfortable inside and I'm very happy.
animando como animaban y me sentí muy cómodo adentro y estoy muy contento.
斯卡洛尼在让你上场之前告诉了你什么？
What did Scaloni tell you before putting you on?
¿Qué te dijo Scaloni antes de ponerte?
他告诉我要移动，要享受，要忘记自己的位置，要接球，要玩得开心。
He had told me to move, to enjoy, to forget about the position, to receive the ball and to have a good time.
Me había dicho que me mueva, que disfrute, que me olvide de la posición, que reciba el balón y que me lo pase bien.
比赛结束后他对你说了什么？
What did he say to you after the game you played?
¿Qué te dijo después del partido que hiciste?
我为自己的一切表示祝贺。
I congratulate myself for everything.
Me felicito por todo.
尼科，和这些怪物一起玩意味着什么？
Nico, what does it mean to play with these monsters?
Nico, ¿qué significa jugar con estos monstruos?
一侧有朱利安、劳塔罗，另一侧有梅西吗？
On one side do you have Julián, Lautaro, on the other side Messi?
¿De un lado le tenés a Julián, a Lautaro, del otro lado a Messi?
这对你来说意味着什么？
What does it mean to you?
¿Qué significa para vos?
这很疯狂，事实是这样玩起来更容易，显然更容易包围自己。
It's crazy, the truth is that it's easier to play that way, obviously it's easier to surround yourself.
Es una locura, la verdad que así es más fácil jugar, obviamente es más fácil rodearte.
这些球员太不可思议了。
These players are incredible.
Estos jugadores son increíbles.
梅西对你说得很好，他指出了你的个性、你的心态。
Messi spoke very well of you, he pointed out your personality, your mentality.
Messi habló muy bien de vos, señaló tu personalidad, tu mentalidad.
在这场比赛之前，你和莱昂内尔、梅西谈论了这些预选赛的哪些内容？
What did you talk about with Lionel, with Messi before this match, about these qualifiers?
¿Qué hablaste con Lionel, con Messi antes de este partido, de estas eliminatorias?
里奥，事实上，他是一个很棒的人，他给了我很多建议，在球场上他让我感觉更舒服。
Leo, the truth is that he is a great person, he has given me a lot of advice and on the field he has made me feel much more comfortable.
Leo, la verdad que es una gran persona, me ha dado muchos consejos y dentro del campo me ha hecho sentirme mucho más cómodo.
他帮助我登上了球场，事实上我非常感谢他。
He helped me get on the field and the truth is that I thank him very much.
Me ayudaba a colocarme en el campo y la verdad es que le agradezco mucho.
正如他们今天所唱的那样，人们已经卖光了。
The people, as they sang today, sold out.
La gente, como cantó hoy, lleno total.
这太疯狂了，与世界上任何其他事情都不一样。
It's crazy, different from anything else in the world.
Es una locura distinto a todo lo que hay en el mundo.
它显示在球场上。
and it shows on the field.
y se nota dentro del campo.
好吧，如果你不知道的话，尼科·帕斯是西班牙人，他出生在特内里费岛，这就是为什么他用那种曲调说话。
Well, in case you don't know, Nico Paz is Spanish, he was born in Tenerife, that's why he speaks with that tune.
Bueno, por si no lo saben, Nico Paz es español, nació en Tenerife, por eso habla con esa tonada.
他的母亲是西班牙人，我们已经说过了，他的父亲巴勃罗·帕斯是一名前球员。
His mother is Spanish, we have already said it, his father Pablo Paz, a former player.
Su mamá es española, ya lo hemos dicho, su papá Pablo Paz, ex jugador.
德尼维斯，费德的前队友。
De Nieves, Fede's former teammate.
De Nieves, ex compañero de Fede.
但这就是为什么他用那样的语气说话并且他​​选择为阿根廷队效力
but that's why he speaks with that tune and he chooses to play for the Argentine team
pero por eso habla con esa tonada y él elige jugar para la selección argentina
我们受到父亲的影响。
and we had the influence of our father.
y tuvimos por influencia del papá.
但母亲是西班牙人，他出生了。
But the mother is Spanish, he was born.
Pero la mamá es española, él nació.
在西班牙的特内里费岛，这就是为什么那首曲子和他刚才所说的话，我想
in Tenerife in Spain, that's why with that tune and with what he just said, I imagine
en tenerife en españa por eso con esa tonada y con lo que acaba de decir imagino
作为人民的他，已经赢得了球迷的心。
of the people, he has already won the hearts of the fans.
de la gente, ya se ganó el corazón de los hinchas.
在此之后还有更多。
And much more after this.
Y mucho más después de esto.
因为它带着一种简单，一种简单、旁白、优雅。
because it entered with a simplicity, with a simplicity, aside, elegance.
porque entró con una sencillez, con una simpleza, aparte, elegancia.
看看它玩起来多么优雅。
Look how elegant it is to play with.
Mirá que es muy elegante para jugar.
他个子很高，步伐也很好。
He is tall, he has good stride.
Es alto, tiene buen tranco.
你必须以中场球员的身份为皇马打进第一个进球。
You have to get to Real Madrid's first goal by playing as a midfielder.
Hay que llegar a la primera del Real Madrid jugando de media punta.
为什么连低等的人都不在那里？
Why aren't they even the inferior ones there?
¿Por qué ni son las inferiores ahí?
非常好。
Very good.
Muy bien.
我们在说什么？
What are we talking about?
¿De qué estamos hablando?
我是左撇子的爱好者，对吧？
I am a lover of left-handed people, right?
Yo soy un enamorado de los zurdos, ¿no?
您是否已经再加一分，还是要再加一分？
Do you already add one more point or do you add one?
Vos ya le ponéis un punto más o le ponéis uno?
对所有人。
To all.
A todos.
做个好人。
To be good.
A ser bien.
做个好人。
To be good.
A ser bien.
左手的东西看起来更好。
The left-handed thing looks better.
Luce más lo del zurdo.
但当然，这里显然是左撇子第一。
But of course, here is obviously the left-handed number one.
Pero claro, acá está obviamente el número uno del zurdo.
看看他是怎么还给她的吧？
Look how he gave it back to her, right?
Mirá cómo se la devolvió, ¿no?
里面。
Inside.
Adentro.
而且，除此之外，他归还它的事实是一种感动，但是......
And, apart from that, the fact that he returns it is a touch, but...
Y, aparte, también que la devuelve es un toque, pero...
接到梅西的传球而又不死心去回传的压力。
The pressure of receiving a pass from Messi and not dying trying to return it.
La presión que es recibir un pase de Messi y no morir en el intento de la devolución.
我该怎么办？
What do I do with this?
¿Qué hago con esto?
这是一枚手榴弹。
It's a grenade.
Es una granada.
为了照顾我，你离开了她。
Taking care of me you left her.
Cuidándome la dejaste.
他让一切变得完美。
And he left it perfect.
Y se la dejó perfecta.
完美的。
Perfect.
Perfecta.
在我们刚刚与……进行的比较中，它表现得非常出色。
It came in fantastically in the comparison we just made with...
Entró fantástico en la comparación que hacíamos recién con...
有时付出的代价...
Sometimes with what it cost...
A veces con lo que le costó a...
歌海娜 (Garnacho) 给歌海娜 (Garnacho) 留下的印象
to Garnacho that Garnacho gave the impression
a Garnacho que Garnacho daba la impresión
有时他会因自己的焦虑而跌倒，对吧？
That sometimes he stumbled a lot with his own anxiety, right?
que a veces tropezaba mucho con su propia ansiedad ¿no?
在我看来，这与有关。
It has to do with, it seems to me.
Tiene que ver con, me parece.
国家队的比赛方式，因为我们也不应该对伯纳乔不公平。
The way the national team plays, because we should not be unfair to Bernacho either.
La manera de jugar de la selección, porque tampoco hay que ser injusto con Bernacho.
球队的比赛方式是一支更具关联性的球队。
The way the team plays, which is a more associative team.
La manera de jugar de la selección, que es una selección más asociativa.
就是打空间和反击，这对尼科帕斯比加纳乔更有利。
which is to play space and counterattack, which favors Nicopas more than Garnacho.
que es de jugar al espacio y al contragolpe, con lo cual esto favorece más a Nicopas que a Garnacho.
其次也是比赛的背景，尼科·帕斯上场，我认为他的比分是 4 或 5 比 0。
Second also the context of the game, in which Nico Paz enters, who I think was 4 or 5 to 0.
Segundo también el contexto del partido, en el que entra Nico Paz, que creo que iba 4 o 5 a 0.
对手，一个已经被击败的对手，一个已经沮丧的对手，他没有提供太多的抵抗，
the rival, a rival already defeated, a rival already frustrated, where he does not offer much resistance, with which
el rival, un rival ya vencido, un rival ya frustrado, donde no ofrece mucha resistencia, con lo cual
尼科·帕斯（Nico Paz）的进入也没有那么复杂。
It is also less complicated for Nico Paz to enter.
A Nico Paz también se le hace menos complicado entrar.
另一方面...
And on the other hand...
Y por otro lado...
草地、队友，所有这些给我的印象是，这让事情变得容易多了。
The grass, the teammates, all of that gives me the impression that it makes it much easier.
el pasto, los compañeros, todo eso me da la impresión que le hace mucho más fácil.
因为阿尔纳乔一定也在看，因为他没有看着我们，并说……这位亲戚怎么样？
Because Arnacho must also be looking, because he is not looking at us and says... How does this relative do?
Porque Arnacho también debe estar mirando, porque no se está mirando nosotros y dice... ¿Cómo hace este parente?
但这是证据，呵呵。
But it's evidence, huh.
Pero es una evidencia, eh.
事实证明，在职业足球方面更有造诣的加纳乔，在融入过程中遇到了更多的困难。
It is evidence that Garnacho, who is more accomplished in professional football, has had more difficulties to insert himself.
Es una evidencia que Garnacho, que está más consumado en el fútbol profesional, ha tenido más dificultades para insertarse.
你没注意到加纳乔如此热心吗？
Didn't you notice Garnacho as eager?
¿No lo notaron como ansioso Garnacho?
我不能。
I couldn't.
No podía.
躺在床上，男人说，该死的男人，你在说什么？
Lying on the bed, the man says, damn man, what are you saying?
Tirado en la cama, el señor dice, joder tío, ¿qué estás diciendo?
最重要的是，他说同样的话。
On top of that he speaks the same.
Encima habla igual.
但这是真的，如果他有空间的话，这种情况就会发生……
But it's true, this happens, if he has space...
Pero es verdad, pasa esto, si él tiene espacio...
它给我的感觉是……来自Arnacho。
The feeling it gave me is... From Arnacho.
La sensación que a mí me daba es... De Arnacho.
我得到的感觉是...
The feeling I got is...
La sensación que me daba es...
远射、自行车射门、中射、球门球，脑子里信息太多，最后
the long shot, the bicycle shot, the center shot, the goal kick, there was so much information in my head that in the end
la tiro larga, tiro bicicleta, tiro el centro, pateo al arco, era tanta información en la cabeza que al final
这个男孩从最简单到最复杂。
This boy went from the simplest to the most complicated.
Este chico fue de lo más sencillo a la complicación.
我钩住，我扔出一堵墙。
I hook, I throw a wall.
Engancho, tiro una pared.
它有一个咨询游戏，因为它的特点是更具吸引力，它更...
It has an advisory game because its characteristic is more engaging, it is more...
Tiene juego asesorativo porque por su característica es más enganche, es más...
糖糖与阿根廷队的比赛密切相关，这是一场与内线相关的比赛。
Sugaring goes more hand in hand with what Argentina plays, which is an associated game on the inside.
La azucaradita va más de la mano a lo que juega Argentina, que es juego asociado por dentro.
因此，在这种情况下，他们比歌海娜拥有更多的资源。
So that's where they have more resources in their favor than Garnacho, in this case.
Entonces ahí es donde tienen más recursos a su favor que Garnacho, en este caso.